<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:03:27 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/introduction/</guid><description>RKVST provides Provenance as a Service that continuously proves Who Did What When to any data asset.
RKVST enables enterprises to build trust in multi-party Assets, including software, devices, and media ensuring processes are fit for purpose to comply with IT controls, corporate policies, and government regulations.
RKVST permanently records shared Asset evidence to bring the right level of trust in data for faster, confident decisions with lower business risk by:</description></item><item><title>Core Concepts</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/core-concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/core-concepts/</guid><description>Tenancies A Tenancy is an Organization&amp;rsquo;s private area within RKVST, containing Asset and Event data. The user who created the Tenancy is the Administrator and has full administrative control over everything in that Tenancy. An Administrator can also create granular Access Policies which allow data from their Tenancy to be shared to other Tenancies; for example, Organization A would share Asset data from their Tenancy to Organization B&amp;rsquo;s Tenancy.
Administrators may invite other user accounts into their Tenancy.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Concepts</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/advanced-concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/advanced-concepts/</guid><description>Assets Central to all RKVST operations are Assets. These are the records that represent the collective &amp;lsquo;Golden Thread&amp;rsquo; of evidence contributed by all stakeholders about a particular thing. Assets can represent anything: a physical object, a smart device, or even a business process. As long as shared accountability needs to be traced and trustworthy, it can be recorded as an RKVST Asset.
RKVST Assets are essentially very simple: a collection of attributes that describe the Asset expressed as a standard JSON document.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Asset</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/creating-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/creating-an-asset/</guid><description>An Asset can be anything: a connected machine, a shipping container, or even a data set. It can be any physical or digital object with an associated name, description, and attributes.
Each Asset will have a history of any actions performed upon it by any actor.
You may share Assets and their history with specific stakeholders using permissioned sharing. RKVST also enables you to publicly attest the provenance of your Assets.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Event Against an Asset</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/creating-an-event-against-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:32:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/creating-an-event-against-an-asset/</guid><description>If you wish to begin tracking your Asset history, you need to create Events.
Asset Creation is the first Event. The more Events recorded against an Asset, the richer and deeper its history becomes.
Events track key moments of an Asset&amp;rsquo;s lifecycle; details of Who Did What When to an Asset.
Before creating an Event, follow this guide to create your first example Asset. Creating Events Create an Event. UI YAML JSON When viewing your Asset, click the Record Event button.</description></item><item><title>Registering a Document Profile Asset</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/registering-a-document-profile-asset/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:11:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/registering-a-document-profile-asset/</guid><description>The RKVST document profile is a set of suggested Asset and Event attributes that allow you to trace the lifecycle of a document.
As it builds on the standard RKVST asset the same processes are used for Permissioned Sharing and Public Attestation.
The following steps will guide you in creating your first Document Profile Asset.
Check out our Core Concepts for more general information on Assets and Document Profile for details of the Document Profile asset and event attributes.</description></item><item><title>Public Attestation</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/public-attestation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/public-attestation/</guid><description>You may wish to attest information to the general public, without the need for viewers to log-in to their RKVST account. Public Assets can be used to publicly assert data, also referred to as Public Attestation. For example, you may attest to data containing a vulnerability report against an OpenSource software package or the maintenance records for a building.
Permissioned Assets can only be shared through the creation of Access Policies.</description></item><item><title>Verify RKVST SCITT Receipts</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/scitt-receipts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/scitt-receipts/</guid><description>What are receipts? Having a receipt for an RKVST Event allows you to prove that you recorded the Event on the RKVST Blockchain, independent of RKVST.
Receipts can be retrieved for Simple Hash Events once they have been confirmed and anchored.
Receipts can be retrieved for Khipu Events once they have been confirmed.
A user may get a receipt for any Event they have recorded on the system. You must be an Administrator for your Tenancy to retrieve receipts for any Event within the Tenancy, including those shared by other organizations.</description></item><item><title>Instaproof</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/instaproof/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:10:19 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/platform/overview/instaproof/</guid><description>Instaproof provides data provenance and authenticity with a simple drag-and-drop.
Instaproof will search amongst the assets that have been registered with the document profile and return a list of all assets that have a matching hash value.
The initial version of a document is registered as a document profile asset. New versions of the document are published as events against that asset. See Document Profile more more information.
Using the Instaproof UI Open Instaproof.</description></item></channel></rss>