<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:57:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/introduction/</guid><description>DataTrails provides Provenance as a Service that continuously proves Who Did What When to all data types.
DataTrails enables enterprises to build trust in data such as documents, images and sound files by ensuring that you know the origin and history of the data that you are using. This can also be applied to multi-party Assets such as software and physical items allowing you to make sure that processes are fit for purpose to comply with IT controls, corporate policies, and government regulations.</description></item><item><title>Core Concepts</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/core-concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/core-concepts/</guid><description>Tenancies A Tenancy is an Organization&amp;rsquo;s private area within DataTrails, containing Asset and Event data that build over time to create an Audit Trail. The user who created the Tenancy is the Administrator and has full administrative control over everything in that Tenancy. An Administrator can also create granular Access Policies which allow data from their Tenancy to be shared to other Tenancies; for example, Organization A would share Asset data from their Tenancy to Organization B&amp;rsquo;s Tenancy.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Concepts</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/advanced-concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/advanced-concepts/</guid><description>Assets and Events The core tenets of the DataTrails platform are Assets and Events. These are the records that represent the collective &amp;lsquo;Golden Thread&amp;rsquo; of evidence contributed by all stakeholders about a particular thing.
Assets can represent anything: a file, a piece of data, a physical thing or even a business process. As long as shared accountability needs to be traced and trustworthy, it can be recorded as a DataTrails Asset.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Asset</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/creating-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/creating-an-asset/</guid><description>An Asset can be anything: a file (a document, an image, a sound file etc.), a software application, a shipping container, or even a physical product. It can be any digital or physical object with an associated name, description, and attributes.
Each Asset will have a history of any actions performed upon it by any actor.
You may share Assets and their history with specific stakeholders using permission sharing. DataTrails also enables you to publicly attest the provenance of your Assets.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Event Against an Asset</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/creating-an-event-against-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:32:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/creating-an-event-against-an-asset/</guid><description>If you wish to begin tracking your Asset history and build an immutable Audit Trail, you need to create Events.
Asset Creation is the first Event. The more Events recorded against an Asset, the richer and deeper its history becomes.
Events track key moments of an Asset&amp;rsquo;s lifecycle; details of Who Did What When to an Asset.
Note: Before creating an Event, follow this guide to create your first Asset. You will need to wait for the Asset to reach COMMITTED state before attempting to record an Event.</description></item><item><title>Registering a Document Profile Asset</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/registering-a-document-profile-asset/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:11:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/registering-a-document-profile-asset/</guid><description>The DataTrails document profile is a set of suggested Asset and Event attributes that allow you to trace the lifecycle of a document.
As it builds on the standard DataTrails asset the same processes are used for Permissioned Sharing and Public Attestation.
The following steps will guide you in creating your first Document Profile Asset.
Note: Check out our Core Concepts for more general information on Assets and Document Profile for details of the Document Profile asset and event attributes.</description></item><item><title>Registering an Event Against a Document Profile Asset</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/registering-an-event-against-a-document-profile-asset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 13:07:55 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/registering-an-event-against-a-document-profile-asset/</guid><description>It is rare for a document to remain unchanged during it&amp;rsquo;s lifetime. Some documents are expected to go though many versions (e.g product documentation) while others (e.g. an employment contract) change much less frequently.
If you need to update your registered Document Profile Asset you can record this as an Event. The Document Profile defines two types of Event; Publish and Withdraw.
Document Registration is the first Event with each new version being recorded as a Publish Event.</description></item><item><title>Instaproof</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/instaproof/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:10:19 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/instaproof/</guid><description>Instaproof allows anonymous access to the Audit Trail of a file. providing data provenance and authenticity with a simple drag-and-drop.
Instaproof will search amongst the Publicly Attested assets that have been registered with the Document Profile and return a list of all assets that have a matching hash value.
The initial version of a document is registered as a document profile asset. New versions of the document are published as events against that asset.</description></item><item><title>Public Attestation</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/public-attestation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/overview/public-attestation/</guid><description>Transparency through Public Attestation Not everything needs to be kept secret.
Using the example of an image in a news report, the publisher needs everyone to be able to see the image but at the same time the viewers of the image want to know that it is genuine while the owner of the image will want to be credited. There needs to be a way for consumers of data to anonymously verify the data that they are consuming is genuine and also where it came from.</description></item></channel></rss>