<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User Patterns on</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/user-patterns/</link><description>Recent content in User Patterns on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 17:42:10 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/user-patterns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Authenticity and Attestation</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/user-patterns/authenticity-and-attestation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/user-patterns/authenticity-and-attestation/</guid><description>A very simple yet powerful pattern for using RKVST is the Authenticity pattern. This is a good choice when dealing with data or documents that need to be broadly proven. In a single action files can be uploaded to RKVST and their integrity, origin, and timestamps can be verified forever. Stakeholders relying on these files can verify that what they see on their screen is authentic and untampered.
Example: Evidential documents and photographs There are a great many documents that serve as evidence in formal discussions: pictures of a traffic accident; education diplomas; contracts; statements of account.</description></item><item><title>Bill of Materials</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/user-patterns/bill-of-materials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/user-patterns/bill-of-materials/</guid><description>A common pattern for tracking asset lifecycles is the Bill of Materials pattern. This is a good choice when dealing with multi-stakeholder systems which change over time, and it is important for the stakeholders to understand the composition of that system no matter who - or what - has changed things.
Modelling such systems in RKVST can help to rapidly answer questions like &amp;ldquo;what is in my estate?&amp;quot;, &amp;ldquo;how did it come to be here?</description></item><item><title>State Machine and Supply Chains</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/user-patterns/state-machine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/user-patterns/state-machine/</guid><description>A common pattern for tracking asset lifecycles is the State Machine pattern. This is a good choice for multi-stakeholder process modelling, particularly where the order of operations is important or activities are triggered by actions of partners. Tracing multi-stakeholder business processes in RKVST not only ensures transparency and accountability among parties but is also faster and more reliable than typical cross-organization data sharing and process management involving phone calls and spreadsheets.</description></item></channel></rss>