<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DataTrails on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in DataTrails on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Archive</title><link>/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 09:25:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>/archive/</guid><description>This section is intended to be a space for articles that are no longer needed but still have content that we do not want to delete.
It is not linked to by any public facing parts of the docs.</description></item><item><title>Sales</title><link>/sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 09:25:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>/sales/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Support</title><link>/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 09:25:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>/support/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>/glossary/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 10:19:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>/glossary/</guid><description>Select an option to to find out more about the terms used by DataTrails.
Common DataTrails Terms: A list of terms used by DataTrails. Reserved Attributes: A list of Asset attributes that are used by the DataTrails platform and have a specific purpose.</description></item><item><title>Use Cases</title><link>/usecases/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 17:42:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>/usecases/</guid><description>DataTrails is a powerful and flexible platform enabling users to record Who Did What &amp;amp; When to any content. To get the best out of the DataTrails it is important to model your real-world assets and business processes efficiently into DataTrails Assets and Events.
The three most common patterns are:
Authenticity and Attestation: proving the state of documents and data at a point in time. Also known as &amp;lsquo;Provenance&amp;rsquo;. Bill of Materials: tracing the contents and composition of assets.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>/contributing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:03:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>/contributing/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Developers</title><link>/developers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/developers/</guid><description>Developers If you are a developer who is looking to easily add provenance to their data, this section is for you. You may be building a new application or looking for a way to add functionality to something that you already use every day.
The DataTrails REST API, python SDK, or the YAML runner provide a simple way for you to integrate a provenance layer into your existing data platform so that you do not need to change the way that your users work.</description></item><item><title>Platform</title><link>/platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/platform/</guid><description>Platform If you are new to DataTrails, this is the place to start.
The foundations of understanding the DataTrails platform are explained in the Overview. This will introduce the basic (and not so basic) concepts and take you through creating your first Asset and registering the first Event of your audit trail.
The Administration section will show you how to manage your Tenancy and control access to your Assets. Check out the sub-sections below for more information!</description></item></channel></rss>