<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:03:27 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/introduction/</guid><description>RKVST is a Data Assurance Service that continuously proves Who Did What When to an Asset.
RKVST enables enterprises to build trust in multi-party Assets, including software and devices, ensuring processes are fit for purpose to comply with IT controls, corporate policies, and government regulations.
RKVST permanently records shared Asset evidence to bring the right level of trust in data for faster, confident decisions with lower business risk by:
Metadata Governance - Empower the right people in organizations to set, enforce, and execute complex data sharing policies.</description></item><item><title>Core Concepts</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/core-concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/core-concepts/</guid><description>Tenancies A Tenancy is an Organization&amp;rsquo;s private area within RKVST, containing Asset and Event data. The user who created the Tenancy is the Administrator and has full administrative control over everything in that Tenancy. An Administrator can also create granular Access Policies which allow data from their Tenancy to be shared to other Tenancies; for example, Organization A would share Asset data from their Tenancy to Organization B&amp;rsquo;s Tenancy.
Administrators may invite other user accounts into their Tenancy.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Concepts</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/advanced-concepts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/advanced-concepts/</guid><description>Assets Central to all RKVST operations are Assets. These are the records that represent the collective &amp;lsquo;Golden Thread&amp;rsquo; of evidence contributed by all stakeholders about a particular thing. Assets can represent anything: a physical object, a smart device, or even a business process. As long as shared accountability needs to be traced and trustworthy, it can be recorded as an RKVST Asset.
RKVST Assets are essentially very simple: a collection of attributes that describe the Asset expressed as a standard JSON document.</description></item><item><title>Identity and Access Management</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/identity-and-access-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/overview/identity-and-access-management/</guid><description>Tenancies and Accounts Each RKVST Tenancy represents an organization, and each RKVST account represents an individual user. There may be multiple accounts within a Tenancy if there are several members within an organization. Additionally, an indivudual user can be part of multiple Tenancies.
How do I add users to my organization? RKVST Invites make it easy to add accounts to your tenancy.
As an administrator, create an invite and send it to the email address of the user you wish to add.</description></item></channel></rss>