<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developer Patterns on</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/</link><description>Recent content in Developer Patterns on</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.2</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 11:12:25 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creating Access Tokens Using a Custom Integration</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/getting-access-tokens-using-app-registrations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:12:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/getting-access-tokens-using-app-registrations/</guid><description>Non-interactive access to the DataTrails platform is managed by creating Integrations with either a Custom Integration or one of the built-in Integrations. This is done using either the Settings or Integrations menus in the DataTrails UI or by using the App Registrations API directly. Note: App Registration is the old name for a Custom Integration. Custom Integrations have a CLIENT_ID and a SECRET, these are used to authenticate with DataTrails IAM endpoints using JSON Web Tokens (JWT).</description></item><item><title>Containers as Assets</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/containers-as-assets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/containers-as-assets/</guid><description>Represent Containers Using DataTrails DataTrails Assets can be used to track the status, contents, location, and other key attributes of containers over time. This can also be done for containers within containers. For example, you may wish to track bags inside boxes that are inside a shipping container being transported on a train.
Create a Container Asset A Container Asset is not a special type of asset, it is a label that is given to an Asset that has been created to represent a container.</description></item><item><title>Namespace</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/namespace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/namespace/</guid><description>Namespace is a tool that can be used to prevent unwanted interactions when multiple users are performing testing in the same Tenancy. Using two separate namespaces prevents collisions that may cause undesirable results by allowing multiple users to interact with the same Assets and Events without interrupting each other.
Namespace can be added as an attribute within the files you are testing, or as a variable in your Bash environment.</description></item><item><title>Archived: Verifying Assets and Events with Simple Hash</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/verifying-with-simple-hash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/verifying-with-simple-hash/</guid><description>Verifying your Simple Hash events provides an additional layer of assurance to your data, so you can ensure that the information you have in your hand at a given time has not changed.
This allows you to check for yourself, and prove to others, that any attestations that you made have not been changed since they were recorded in DataTrails.
To verify your data, you may use the DataTrails Simple Hash tool, available on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Document Profile</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/document-profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/document-profile/</guid><description>The DataTrails document profile is a set of suggested Asset and Event attributes that allow you to trace the lifecycle of a document.
Profile Attribute Namespace The document_ prefix is used to designate attributes that are part of the profile. Some of these are interpreted by DataTrails and others are guidelines.
Document Profile Asset Attributes Asset Attributes Meaning Requirement arc_profile Designates that the Asset follows the document profile Required, set as Document document_hash_value Hash of the most recently published version of the document Required document_hash_alg Algorithm used to compute document_hash_value (currently, only SHA-256 is supported) Required document_document Attachment containing the most recently uploaded version of the document being traced.</description></item><item><title>Software Package Profile</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/software-package-profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:56:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/software-package-profile/</guid><description>Overview The DataTrails Software Package profile is a set of suggested Asset and Event attributes that enable the recording of an immutable and verifiable Software Bill of Materials (SBOM).
The NTIA describes a SBOM as &amp;ldquo;a formal record containing the details and supply chain relationships of various components used in building software.&amp;rdquo;
Software Package Profile Asset Attributes NTIA Attribute Asset Attributes Meaning Requirement Author Name sbom_author The name of the Package Author Required Supplier Name sbom_supplier The name of the Package Supplier Required Component Name sbom_component,(arc_display_name if appropriate) The name of the Software Package Required Version String sbom_version The version of the Software Package Required Unique Identifier sbom_uuid A unique identifier for the Package, DataTrails provides a Unique ID per asset but it may be preferred to include an existing internal reference instead Required N/A sbom_repo Link to the Git Repo of the Component Optional N/A sbom_release_notes Link to the release notes of the package version Optional N/A sbom_license The licensing used by the component (if specified) Optional Note: Software Package Profile Attribute Namespace</description></item><item><title>Quickstart: SCITT Statements (Preview)</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/scitt-api/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 13:49:35 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/developers/developer-patterns/scitt-api/</guid><description>The SCITT API is currently in preview and subject to change The Supply Chain Integrity, Transparency and Trust (SCITT) initiative is a set of IETF standards for managing the compliance and auditability of goods and services across end-to-end supply chains. SCITT supports the ongoing verification of goods and services where the authenticity of entities, evidence, policy, and artifacts can be assured and the actions of entities can be guaranteed to be authorized, non-repudiable, immutable, and auditable.</description></item></channel></rss>