<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developer Patterns on</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/</link><description>Recent content in Developer Patterns on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:14:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Access Tokens using App Registrations</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/getting-access-tokens-using-app-registrations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:12:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/getting-access-tokens-using-app-registrations/</guid><description>Non-interactive access to the RKVST platform is managed by creating Applications with App Registrations, using either the Settings Menu in the UI or by using the App Registrations API directly.
Applications have a CLIENT_ID and SECRET that can then be used to authenticate to RKVST IAM endpoints to issue a token (JWT) for accessing the rest of the RKVST API.
This authentication flow uses the industry-standard OIDC &amp;lsquo;Client Credentials&amp;rsquo; Flow.</description></item><item><title>Containers as Assets</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/containers-as-assets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/containers-as-assets/</guid><description>Represent Containers Using RKVST RKVST Assets can be used to track the status, contents, location, and other key attributes of containers over time. This can also be done for containers within containers. For example, you may wish to track bags inside boxes that are inside a shipping container being transported on a train.
Create a Container Asset Creating an Asset to represent a container is the same as creating any other asset.</description></item><item><title>Namespace</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/namespace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/namespace/</guid><description>Namespace is a tool that can be used to prevent unwanted interactions when multiple users are performing testing in the same Tenancy. Using two separate namespaces prevents collisions that may cause undesirable results by allowing multiple users to interact with the same Assets and Events without interrupting each other.
Namespace can be added as an attribute within the files you are testing, or as a variable in your Bash environment.</description></item><item><title>Verifying Assets and Events with Simple Hash</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/verifying-with-simple-hash/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/verifying-with-simple-hash/</guid><description>Verifying your Simple Hash events provides an additional layer of assurance to your data, so you can ensure the information you have at a given time has not changed.
To verify your data, you may use the RKVST Simple Hash tool, available on GitHub.
Please note that with Simple Hash, Events are committed to the RKVST blockchain as a batch. Events with the blue tick have been committed to the blockchain as part of a batch, and will have a Transaction ID.</description></item><item><title>Document Profile</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/document-profile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/developers/developer-patterns/document-profile/</guid><description>The RKVST document profile is a set of suggested Asset and Event attributes that allow you to trace the lifecycle of a document.
Profile Attribute Namespace The document_ prefix is used to designate attributes that are part of the profile. Some of these are interpreted by RKVST and others are guidelines. Document Profile Asset Attributes Asset Attributes Meaning Requirement arc_profile Designates that the Asset follows the document profile Required, set as Document document_hash_value Hash of the most recently published version of the document Required document_hash_alg Algorithm used to compute document_hash_value (currently, only SHA-256 is supported) Required document_document Attachment containing the most recently uploaded version of the document being traced.</description></item></channel></rss>