<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Glossary on</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/glossary/</link><description>Recent content in Glossary on</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.2</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:39:44 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.datatrails.ai/glossary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Common DataTrails Terms</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/glossary/common-datatrails-terms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:39:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/glossary/common-datatrails-terms/</guid><description>Select a term for more information.
Term Definition ABAC Attribute-Based Access Control; policy that allows you to grant fine-grain access to members of your Tenancy access policy grants chosen Asset and Event access to stakeholders actor person/machine/software integration that created a particular entry on the provenance record administrator user with permission to see all Asset and Event information within a Tenancy, and to grant access to other users asset a DataTrails Asset is an entry in your tenancy, which has a collection of attributes that describes its current state and a complete life history of Events asset attributes key-value pairs that represent information about an Asset asset ID the permanent unique identifier for an Asset, under which all provenance information (Events) can be found audit trail a formal record of activities (Events) that are made against a piece of data (an Asset) bearer token access token for DataTrails API; created using Custom Integration credentials behaviors detail what class of events in an Asset lifecycle you might wish to record compliance policy user-defined rule sets that Assets can be tested against custom integration client ID and client secret credentials that are used to access the DataTrails API.</description></item><item><title>Reserved Attributes</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/glossary/reserved-attributes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:39:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/glossary/reserved-attributes/</guid><description>Reserved attributes are asset attributes that are used by the DataTrails platform and have a specific purpose. All reserved attributes have the arc_ prefix.
Select an attribute to see an example of it in use.
Asset Attributes Attribute Meaning arc_description brief description of Asset or Event being recorded arc_display_name friendly name identifier for Assets, Events, and policies arc_display_type classification of the type of Asset being traced that can be used for grouping or access control arc_home_location_identity physical location to which an Asset nominally &amp;lsquo;belongs&amp;rsquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>