<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quickstart on</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/</link><description>Recent content in Quickstart on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:03:27 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Who Did What When to an Asset?</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/when-who-did-what-to-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/when-who-did-what-to-an-asset/</guid><description>Enterprise developers are challenged to build apps that track usage and build trust in multi-party data while meeting assurance, governance, and compliance needs of the business. Assurance needs to be continuous and system-wide.
Unlike forming your own blockchain consortium, committing to expensive integrations or managing spreadsheets, RKVST brings the right level of trust in data and confidence in decisions with a single line of code integration at a fraction of cost and time to value.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Asset</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/creating-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/creating-an-asset/</guid><description>An Asset can be anything: a Connected Machine, a Shipping Container or even a Data Set. It can be any physical or digital object with an associated Name, Description, and Attributes.
Each Asset will have a history of any actions performed upon it by any actor.
The creation of an Asset is the first Event in its lifecycle. The following steps will guide you in creating your first Asset.
Creating an Asset Using the Sidebar, select Add Asset.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Event Against an Asset</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/creating-an-event-against-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:32:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/creating-an-event-against-an-asset/</guid><description>If you wish to begin tracking your Asset history, you need to create Events.
Asset Creation is the first Event and the more Events recorded against an Asset, the richer and deeper its history becomes.
Events track key moments of an Asset&amp;rsquo;s lifecycle; details of Who Did What When to an Asset.
Creating Events When viewing your Asset click the Record Event button. Recording an Event You will see the following screen, where you can enter an Event type and description.</description></item><item><title>Grouping Assets by Location</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/grouping-assets-by-location/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:32:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/grouping-assets-by-location/</guid><description>Locations associate an Asset with a &amp;lsquo;home&amp;rsquo; that can help when governing sharing policies with OBAC and ABAC. Locations do not need pinpoint precision and can be named by site, building or other logical grouping.
It may still be useful to indicate an Asset&amp;rsquo;s origin. For example, if tracking traveling consultant&amp;rsquo;s Laptops, you may still wish to associate them with a &amp;lsquo;home&amp;rsquo; office.
Creating a Location In the Dashboard select Add Location in the Sidebar.</description></item><item><title>Managing Access to an Asset With ABAC</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/managing-access-to-an-asset-with-abac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:33:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/managing-access-to-an-asset-with-abac/</guid><description>Caution: You will only have access to the Access Policies screen if you are a Root User in your Organization. Attribute Based Access Control (ABAC) policies can be used to control access to Assets, their Attributes and Events within a single Organization.
Specifically, ABAC policies are created by Root Users to then share information with Non-Root Users in the same Tenancy.
ABAC policies can be granular, with users allowed to see only single Attributes at a time if wished.</description></item><item><title>Sharing Assets With OBAC</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/sharing-assets-with-obac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:33:31 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/quickstart/sharing-assets-with-obac/</guid><description>Caution: You will only have access to the Access Policies screen if you are a Root User in your organization. Warning: To use OBAC you will need to share with an external organization. Organization Based Access Control (OBAC) policies have a lot in common with Attribute Based Access Control (ABAC) policies; they apply the same controls with two different classes of Actor.
Where they differ is that OBAC shares only with Root Users of an External Organization; the External Root User must then apply ABAC to establish appropriate access for their own organization&amp;rsquo;s Non-Root Users.</description></item></channel></rss>