<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Administration on</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/</link><description>Recent content in Administration on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:14:18 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Identity and Access Management</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/identity-and-access-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 10:57:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/identity-and-access-management/</guid><description>Tenancies and Accounts Each DataTrails Tenancy represents an organization, and each DataTrails account represents an individual user. There may be multiple accounts within a Tenancy if there are several members within an organization. Additionally, an individual user can be part of multiple Tenancies.
How do I add users to my organization? DataTrails Invites make it easy to add accounts to your tenancy.
As an administrator, create an invite and send it to the email address of the user you wish to add.</description></item><item><title>Verified Domain</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/verified-domain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/verified-domain/</guid><description>What is domain verification? Domain verification assures that actors claiming to be part of an organization are authorized to share information on their behalf. If an organization&amp;rsquo;s Tenancy has been verified by the DataTrails team, a badge indicating that they have been verified will appear next to their domain name.
Note: Having a verified domain is different from a Tenant Display Name. Tenant display names are internal, appearing only within your own Tenancy, and are not visible to anyone you share with.</description></item><item><title>Managing Access to an Asset With ABAC</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/managing-access-to-an-asset-with-abac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:33:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/managing-access-to-an-asset-with-abac/</guid><description>Caution: You will only have access to the Access Policies screen if you are an Administrator in your organization. Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) policies can be used to control access to Assets, their attributes, and Events within a single organization.
Specifically, ABAC policies are created by Administrators to share information with Non-Administrators in the same Tenancy.
ABAC policies can be granular, with users only allowed to see single attributes at a time.</description></item><item><title>Sharing Assets outside your Tenant</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/sharing-assets-outside-your-tenant/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:33:31 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/sharing-assets-outside-your-tenant/</guid><description>Organization-Based Access Control (OBAC) policies allow you, as a tenant administrator, to share assets and events from your tenancy with an administrator of another tenant. This permissioned sharing allows you to grant access, whether read/write or read-only, to people outside of your organization.
OBAC policies have a lot in common with Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) policies; they apply the same controls with two different classes of actor. Where they differ is that OBAC shares only with Administrators of an external organization.</description></item><item><title>Compliance Policies</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/compliance-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/compliance-policies/</guid><description>Creating a Compliance Policy Compliance Policies are user-defined rule sets that Assets can be tested against. Compliance Policies only need to be created once; all applicable Assets will be tested against that policy thereafter.
For example, a policy might assert that “Maintenance Alarm Events must be addressed by a Maintenance Report Event, recorded within 72 hours of the alarm”. This creates a Compliance Policy in the system which any Asset can be tested against as needed.</description></item><item><title>Grouping Assets by Location</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/grouping-assets-by-location/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:32:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/grouping-assets-by-location/</guid><description>Locations associate an Asset with a &amp;lsquo;home&amp;rsquo; that can help when governing sharing policies with OBAC and ABAC. Locations do not need pinpoint precision and can be named by site, building, or other logical grouping.
It may be useful to indicate an Asset&amp;rsquo;s origin. For example, if tracking traveling consultant&amp;rsquo;s laptops, you may wish to associate them with a &amp;lsquo;home&amp;rsquo; office.
Caution: It is important to recognize that the location does not necessarily denote the Asset’s current position in space; it simply determines which facility the Asset belongs to.</description></item><item><title>Dropbox Integration</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/dropbox-integration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:18:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/platform/administration/dropbox-integration/</guid><description>The Dropbox Integration This integration allows you to connect your DataTrails tenancy directly with Dropbox to automatically record and maintain the provenance metadata of your files in an immutable audit trail.
DataTrails uses transparent and auditable distributed ledger technology to maintain an immutable trail of provenance metadata independent of, but in concert with, the original file in Dropbox. The original data never enters the DataTrails system and remains on Dropbox. The provenance metadata that is recorded in the immutable audit trail can be shared and verified globally completely independently of the data itself.</description></item></channel></rss>