<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RKVST Basics on</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/</link><description>Recent content in RKVST Basics on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:03:27 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Access Tokens using App Registrations</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/getting-access-tokens-using-app-registrations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:12:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/getting-access-tokens-using-app-registrations/</guid><description>Non-interactive access to the RKVST platform is managed by creating Applications with App Registrations, using either the Manage RKVST Menu in the UI or by using the App Registrations API directly.
Applications have a CLIENT_ID and SECRET that can then be used to authenticate to RKVST IAM Endpoints to issue a token (JWT) for accessing the rest of the RKVST API.
This authentication flow uses the industry-standard OIDC &amp;lsquo;Client Credentials&amp;rsquo; Flow.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Asset</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/creating-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/creating-an-asset/</guid><description>An Asset can be anything: a Connected Machine, a Shipping Container, or even a Data Set. It can be any physical or digital object with an associated Name, Description, and Attributes.
Each Asset will have a history of any actions performed upon it by any actor.
You may share Assets and their history with specific stakeholders using permissioned sharing. RKVST also enables you to publicly attest the provenance of your Assets.</description></item><item><title>Creating an Event Against an Asset</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/creating-an-event-against-an-asset/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:32:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/creating-an-event-against-an-asset/</guid><description>If you wish to begin tracking your Asset history, you need to create Events.
Asset Creation is the first Event. The more Events recorded against an Asset, the richer and deeper its history becomes.
Events track key moments of an Asset&amp;rsquo;s lifecycle; details of Who Did What When to an Asset.
Before creating an Event, follow this guide to create your first example Asset. Creating Events Create an Event. UI YAML JSON When viewing your Asset, click the Record Event button.</description></item><item><title>Grouping Assets by Location</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/grouping-assets-by-location/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:32:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/grouping-assets-by-location/</guid><description>Locations associate an Asset with a &amp;lsquo;home&amp;rsquo; that can help when governing sharing policies with OBAC and ABAC. Locations do not need pinpoint precision and can be named by site, building, or other logical grouping.
It may be useful to indicate an Asset&amp;rsquo;s origin. For example, if tracking traveling consultant&amp;rsquo;s Laptops, you may wish to associate them with a &amp;lsquo;home&amp;rsquo; office.
Creating a Location Create your Location. UI YAML JSON In the Dashboard, select Add Location in the Sidebar.</description></item><item><title>Managing Access to an Asset With ABAC</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/managing-access-to-an-asset-with-abac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:33:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/managing-access-to-an-asset-with-abac/</guid><description>Caution: You will only have access to the Access Policies screen if you are a Root User in your Organization. Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) policies can be used to control access to Assets, their Attributes, and Events within a single Organization.
Specifically, ABAC policies are created by Root Users to share information with Non-Root Users in the same Tenancy.
ABAC policies can be granular, with users allowed to see only single Attributes at a time, if wished.</description></item><item><title>Sharing Assets With OBAC</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/sharing-assets-with-obac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 15:33:31 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/rkvst-basics/sharing-assets-with-obac/</guid><description>Caution: You will only have access to the Access Policies screen if you are a Root User in your organization. Warning: To use OBAC you will need to share with an external organization. Organization-Based Access Control (OBAC) policies have a lot in common with Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) policies; they apply the same controls with two different classes of Actor.
Where they differ is that OBAC shares only with Root Users of an External Organization; the External Root User must then apply ABAC to establish appropriate access for their own organization&amp;rsquo;s Non-Root Users.</description></item></channel></rss>