<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Use Cases on</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/</link><description>Recent content in Use Cases on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 14:03:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Responsible AI</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/responsible-ai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 11:33:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/responsible-ai/</guid><description>As AI technologies become more common the need for trust in AI increases at a greater rate. There is a need to trust the AI model, the dataset that trains the AI machine, the statements about governance and compliance made by the AI vendor before you can trust the output of the AI machine.
Responsible AI includes an ethical and legal viewpoint to ensure that AI works for the good of society, fundamental to this is Trust and Transparency.</description></item><item><title>Authenticity of Media and Files</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/authenticity-media-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/authenticity-media-files/</guid><description>A very simple yet powerful pattern for using DataTrails is the Authenticity pattern. This is a good choice when dealing with data or documents where trust, integrity and authenticity are more important than secrecy. This could be data that is shared between business partners or more simply the relationship between creators and consumers of digital media.
The DataTrails platform separates data from its provenance metadata. By recording the metadata in the DataTrails platform it becomes an irrefutable record of the origin, provenance, integrity and authenticity of the media asset.</description></item><item><title>Supply Chain: Process Governance and Modelling</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/sc-state-machine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 14:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/sc-state-machine/</guid><description>A common pattern for tracking an Asset lifecycle is the State Machine pattern for Multi-party business processes. This is a good choice for multi-stakeholder process modelling, particularly where the order of operations is important or activities are triggered by actions of partners. Tracing multi-stakeholder business processes in DataTrails not only ensures transparency and accountability among parties, but is also faster and more reliable than typical cross-organization data sharing and process management involving phone calls and spreadsheets.</description></item><item><title>Supply Chain: Asset Lifecycle</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/sc-asset-lifecycle/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 14:02:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/sc-asset-lifecycle/</guid><description>Tracking and tracing the lifecycle of physical Assets - from IoT Devices (embedded sensors, handheld equipment) to a whole distribution depot - is a key strength of DataTrails. The ability to collect and examine the entire life history of critical Assets - their provenance - is crucial to building secure and trustworthy systems.
This also applies to digital assets such as software applications, equipment firmware, images and documents. Every item involved in the supply chain has a lifecycle.</description></item><item><title>Supply Chain: Chain of Custody</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/sc-chain-of-custody/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 14:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/sc-chain-of-custody/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Multi-party business processes&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Asset lifecycle tracing&amp;rdquo; are examples of a more general pattern: Supply Chain Handling.
The &amp;lsquo;State Machine&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Lifecycle Tracing&amp;rsquo; pattens are very similar, but the former puts a greater emphasis on modeling and tracing the Events while the latter concentrates more on the evolving state of the Assets. Combining these concepts makes it possible to easily trace complex multi-party supply chains without stakeholders having to adapt to each other&amp;rsquo;s ways of working.</description></item><item><title>Bill of Materials</title><link>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/bill-of-materials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:18:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.datatrails.ai/usecases/bill-of-materials/</guid><description>A common pattern for tracking an asset&amp;rsquo;s lifecycle is the Bill of Materials pattern. This is a good choice when dealing with multi-stakeholder systems which change over time, and it is important for the stakeholders to understand the composition of that system no matter who - or what - has changed things.
Modelling such systems in DataTrails can help to rapidly answer questions like &amp;ldquo;what is in my estate?&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;how did it come to be here?</description></item></channel></rss>