<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup and Administration on</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/</link><description>Recent content in Setup and Administration on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:03:27 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Registering Your Azure Active Directory With RKVST</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/registering-your-azure-active-directory-with-rkvst/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:10:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/registering-your-azure-active-directory-with-rkvst/</guid><description>To obtain access to your RKVST tenancy you need to:
Share your Azure Directory ID with Jitsuin. You will then receive a link to access RKVST. Finding Your Tenant ID Browse to portal.azure.com and open the Azure Active Directory service from the portal menu.
Azure Portal Locate the Tenant ID displayed on the Active Directory Overview blade and send this to Jitsuin.
Tenant ID Note: This identifier is not sensitive information.</description></item><item><title>Assign Users to RKVST for Interactive Use</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/assign-users-to-rkvst-for-interactive-use/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:11:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/assign-users-to-rkvst-for-interactive-use/</guid><description>To enable access for individual users to your RKVST tenant:
Assign Users to the RKVST Enterprise application. Grant assigned users the appropriate RKVST roles. This Microsoft Guide provides the general details for assigning users and their roles.
Locate your RKVST Enterprise Application Having completed admin consent, locate the enterprise application principals for your RKVST.
There will be two Homepage URLs which match the FQDN for the link you received.</description></item><item><title>Configuring App Registrations for Non-Interactive Use</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/configuring-app-registrations-for-non-interactive-use/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:12:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/configuring-app-registrations-for-non-interactive-use/</guid><description>Non-interactive access to the RKVST platform is managed by creating Applications with App Registrations, using either the Manage RKVST Menu in the UI or by using the App Registrations API directly.
Applications have a CLIENT_ID and SECRET that can then be used to authenticate to RKVST IAM Endpoints to issue a token (JWT) for accessing the rest of the RKVST API.
This authentication flow uses the industry-standard OIDC &amp;lsquo;Client Credentials&amp;rsquo; Flow.</description></item><item><title>Getting Access Tokens Using Client Secret</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/getting-access-tokens-using-client-secret/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:13:48 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/setup-and-administration/getting-access-tokens-using-client-secret/</guid><description>Having completed the steps at App Registration, and taken note of the CLIENT ID and the SECRET, a token can be obtained with the following command.
Replace ${CLIENTID} with the application id, and ${SECRET} with your secret from the application registration.
$ RESPONSE=$(curl \ https://app.rkvst.io/archivist/iam/v1/appidp/token \ --data-urlencode &amp;#34;grant_type=client_credentials&amp;#34; \ --data-urlencode &amp;#34;client_id=${CLIENTID}&amp;#34; \ --data-urlencode &amp;#34;client_secret=${SECRET}&amp;#34;) $ TOKEN=$(echo -n $RESPONSE | jq .access_token | tr -d &amp;#39;&amp;#34;&amp;#39;) Testing Access To confirm access token configuration, use the shell command (above) to obtain an access token.</description></item></channel></rss>