<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup and Administration on</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/</link><description>Recent content in Setup and Administration on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 12:03:27 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Registering Your Azure Active Directory With RKVST</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/registering-your-azure-active-directory-with-rkvst/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:10:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/registering-your-azure-active-directory-with-rkvst/</guid><description>To obtain access to your Jitsuin RKVST Instance you need to:
Share your Azure Directory ID to Jitsuin. You will then receive a link to your RKVST Instance. Finding Your Tenant ID Browse to portal.azure.com and open the Azure Active Directory service from the portal menu.
Azure Portal !-- Button trigger modal -- Locate the Tenant ID displayed on the Active Directory Overview blade and send this to Jitsuin.</description></item><item><title>Assign Users to RKVST for Interactive Use</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/assign-users-to-rkvst-for-interactive-use/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:11:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/assign-users-to-rkvst-for-interactive-use/</guid><description>To enable access for individual users to your Jitsuin RKVST:
Assign Users to the Jitsuin RKVST Enterprise application. Grant assigned users the appropriate Jitsuin RKVST roles. This Microsoft Guide provides the general details for assigning users and their roles.
Locate your Jitsuin RKVST Enterprise Application Having completed admin consent, locate the enterprise application principals for your Jitsuin RKVST.
There will be two Homepage URLs which match the FQDN for the link you received.</description></item><item><title>Configuring Azure Clients for Non-Interactive Use</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/configuring-azure-clients-for-non-interactive-use/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:12:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/configuring-azure-clients-for-non-interactive-use/</guid><description>To enable non-interactive access to Jitsuin RKVST APIs:
Create an Application Registration in your Azure Active Directory. Grant an API access permission for the registration referring to the Jitsuin RKVST API Create a Client Secret Note: Certificate based assertion of identity is fully supported. See client_assertion_type and client_assertion in the official Azure Documentation. Create an Application Registration Adding a New App Registration !-- Button trigger modal -- Choose any name you like.</description></item><item><title>Getting Access Tokens Using Client Secret</title><link>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/getting-access-tokens-using-client-secret/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 11:13:48 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.jitsuin.com/docs/setup-and-administration/getting-access-tokens-using-client-secret/</guid><description>Having completed the steps at Application Registration, and taken note of the Application ID and the secret, a token can be obtained with the following command.
Replace ${API_APP_ID} with the application id, and ${API_APP_SECRET} with your secret from the application registration; ${FQDN} is the FQDN for your Jitsuin RKVST.
${TENANT} is your directory id, see how to locate your Tenant here.
$ RESPONSE=$(curl \ https://login.microsoftonline.com/${TENANT}/oauth2/token\ --data-urlencode &amp;#34;grant_type=client_credentials&amp;#34; \ --data-urlencode &amp;#34;client_id=${API_APP_ID}&amp;#34; \ --data-urlencode &amp;#34;client_secret=${API_APP_SECRET}&amp;#34; \ --data-urlencode &amp;#34;resource=https://${FQDN}&amp;#34;) $ TOKEN=$(echo -n $RESPONSE | jq .</description></item></channel></rss>