<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Compliance Policies</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/beyond-the-basics/compliance-policies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/beyond-the-basics/compliance-policies/</guid><description>Creating a Compliance Policy Compliance policies are user-defined rule sets that Assets can be tested against. Compliance policies only need to be created once; all applicable Assets will be tested against that policy thereafter.
For example, a policy might assert that “Maintenance Alarm Events must be addressed by a Maintenance Report Event, recorded within 72 hours of the alarm”. This creates a Compliance Policy in the system which any Asset can be tested against as needed.</description></item><item><title>Public Attestation</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/beyond-the-basics/public-attestation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/beyond-the-basics/public-attestation/</guid><description>You may wish to attest information to the general public, without the need for viewers to log-in to their RKVST account. Public Assets can be used to publicly assert data, also referred to as Public Attestation. For example, you may attest to data containing a vulnerability report against an OpenSource software package or the maintenance records for a building.
Permissioned Assets can only be shared through the creation of Access Policies.</description></item><item><title>Verified Domain</title><link>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/beyond-the-basics/verified-domain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 14:52:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.rkvst.com/docs/beyond-the-basics/verified-domain/</guid><description>What is domain verification? Domain verification assures that actors claiming to be part of an organization are authorized to share information on their behalf. If an organization&amp;rsquo;s tenancy has been verified by the RKVST team, a badge indicating that they have been verified will appear next to their domain name.
Note: Having a verified domain is different from a Tenant Display Name. Tenant display names are internal, appearing only within your own tenancy, and are not visible to anyone you share with.</description></item></channel></rss>