<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Formatting Content on</title><link>https://jitsuin-inc.github.io/rkvst-docs/contributing/formatting-content/</link><description>Recent content in Formatting Content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 19:14:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jitsuin-inc.github.io/rkvst-docs/contributing/formatting-content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Basic Markdown Formatting</title><link>https://jitsuin-inc.github.io/rkvst-docs/contributing/formatting-content/basic-markdown-formatting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 19:23:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jitsuin-inc.github.io/rkvst-docs/contributing/formatting-content/basic-markdown-formatting/</guid><description>Doks uses Goldmark markdown which is primarily Github-flavoured.
The examples below follow our Style Guide.
Headings Warning: We do not allow # Header 1 sizing, this should only be added by the title of the article, use ## Header 2 sizing and below for in-article headers. Headings in markdown can be added using the # character at the beginning of a line of text, the more# you use the smaller the heading will be.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Formatting</title><link>https://jitsuin-inc.github.io/rkvst-docs/contributing/formatting-content/advanced-formatting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 19:23:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jitsuin-inc.github.io/rkvst-docs/contributing/formatting-content/advanced-formatting/</guid><description>As Doks is based on Hugo it has many more extensible formatting options, including some custom tools we have added ourselves to enhance the delivery of documentation overall.
The examples below follow our Style Guide.
Code and Codeblocks There are three different ways to present code and references in Jitsuin Documentation.
Inline Code When talking about a single word, line of code or attribute in a whole sentence you can use single backticks (`) to highlight the specific word or phrase.</description></item><item><title>Style Guide</title><link>https://jitsuin-inc.github.io/rkvst-docs/contributing/formatting-content/style-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 19:23:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jitsuin-inc.github.io/rkvst-docs/contributing/formatting-content/style-guide/</guid><description>It is important in any documentation to have a readable, sane and consistent experience, to that end we have defined some guidelines to ensure all content meets the same standard.
Documentation Structure Content is organised at a directory level using the standard Hugo format, we then have four seperate areas of content.
Typically, only Docs should be edited but permission to add to the other sections will be decided on a case by case basis by Jitsuin Emplyees and Organizational Reviewers.</description></item></channel></rss>